[
    {
        "id": "001",
        "decks": [
            {
                "id": "deck1",
                "name": "Turkish - Set 1",
                "language": "Turkish",
                "cards": [
                    {
                        "id": "card1",
                        "language": "Turkish",
                        "front": "Merhaba",
                        "back": "Hello"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "card2",
                        "language": "Turkish",
                        "front": "Güle güle",
                        "back": "Goodbye"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "card3",
                        "language": "Turkish",
                        "front": "Teşekkür ederim",
                        "back": "Thank you"
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "id": "deck2",
                "name": "Russian - Set 1",
                "language": "Russian",
                "cards": [
                    {
                        "id": "card1",
                        "language": "Russian",
                        "front": "Здравствуйте",
                        "back": "Hello"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "card2",
                        "language": "Russian",
                        "front": "До свидания",
                        "back": "Goodbye"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "card3",
                        "language": "Russian",
                        "front": "Спасибо",
                        "back": "Thank you"
                    }
                ]
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "002",
        "decks": [
            {
                "id": "deck1",
                "name": "Russian - Set 1",
                "language": "Russian",
                "cards": [
                    {
                        "id": "card1",
                        "language": "Russian",
                        "front": "Здравствуйте",
                        "back": "Hello"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "card2",
                        "language": "Russian",
                        "front": "До свидания",
                        "back": "Goodbye"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "card3",
                        "language": "Russian",
                        "front": "Спасибо",
                        "back": "Thank you"
                    }
                ]
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "003",
        "decks": [
            {
                "id": "deck1",
                "name": "Hindi - Set 1",
                "language": "Hindi",
                "cards": [
                    {
                        "id": "card1",
                        "language": "Hindi",
                        "front": "नमस्ते",
                        "back": "Hello"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "card2",
                        "language": "Hindi",
                        "front": "अलविदा",
                        "back": "Goodbye"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "card3",
                        "language": "Hindi",
                        "front": "धन्यवाद",
                        "back": "Thank you"
                    }
                ]
            }
        ]
    }
]